<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- <?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="temp.xsl"?> -->
<root>
	<items>
<!-- 		<item> -->
<!-- 			<timestamp>2015-12-00T00:00</timestamp> -->
<!-- 			<title></title> -->
<!-- 			<description></description> -->
<!-- 			<links> -->
<!-- 				<link> -->
<!-- 					<label>forum</label> -->
<!-- 					<url></url> -->
<!-- 				</link> -->
<!-- 			</links> -->
<!-- 		</item> -->
		
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-12-04T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Upcoming hard-fork</title>
			<description>
				<p>A series of changes to be rolled out in a single hard-fork:</p>
				<p>(1) Refund order creation fees when the order is cancelled</p>
				<p>(2) Fix Referral Program cash-back bug</p>
				<p>(3) Fix margin call price so that is not called unless the feed is below/above the call price (this should prevent a lot of margin calls from occurring)</p>
				<p>(4) Liquidity maker/taker differentiation for the purpose of allocating trading fees to stimulate liquidity - in the form of a new flag on assets (both SmartCoins &amp; UIA) that the issuers will be able to control</p>
			</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>soundcloud</label>
					<url>https://soundcloud.com/beyond-bitcoin-hangouts/beyond-bitcoin-hangout-12-04-2015-s3</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-12-03T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Forced settlement issue is re-enabled</title>
			<description>The main reason of the controversy, i.e. inaccurate price feeds for CNY, has been successfully addressed by upgrading the price feed script. Committee members have created a proposal that re-enables the forced settlement feature and it has become effective after most committee members supported it.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20391.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>cryptofresh</label>
					<url>http://cryptofresh.com/p/1.10.19</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-12-02T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Bitshares UI 2.0.151202 released</title>
			<description>This release is part of the regular weekly upgrades for the GUI. Changes are available immediately in the web wallet or download the latest light client.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20396.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-30T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Forced settlement issue</title>
			<description>The recent release of GUI wallet introduces a 'Force Settlement' button. Some people say that this function allows users to exploit a "loophole" in the bitCNY market and "gain profit at the expense of the bitCNY providers". Others (including BM) say those changes have been discussed in the past and there are tradeoffs that must be made, so there is nothing "new", "unexpected" or "flawed" in how the market is behaving.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20299.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20356.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20287.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-27T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Fee Backed Assets</title>
			<description>This new kind of digital asset trades like any of the others but has fascinating new properties. There could be a new asset for every new revenue generating feature in the whole ecosystem. Developers recoup their costs by selling (or pre-selling) these revenue generating software devices (or keeping them to earn the revenue they produce).</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20286.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-25T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>We have professional Project Coordinator for the GUI</title>
			<description>Worker proposal by wmbutler has passed which means that from now on the efforts of our GUI developers will be professionally coordinated/managed. We can expect weekly upgrades for the GUI.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20144.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>docs</label>
					<url>https://docs.google.com/document/d/14d9bBAyUoB9wcBpFnYoGpE1MF0RnOwMKpF2Z8eh0QkI/edit?usp=sharing</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-23T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>New Stealth Transfer Worker</title>
			<description>BM has been approached by a community member who has offered to cover the $45,000 to implement stealth transfers in the GUI *IF* he can get his money back through stealth transfer fees.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20205.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-23T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>CNX to license Graphene and Graphene-UI under BSD</title>
			<description>All features from all blockchains based upon Graphene can now be adopted by their brother and sister chains. It means that all public chains benefit from developments on other similarly licensed chains.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20209.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-20T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>CCEDK Launch OBITS on OpenLedger</title>
			<description>CCEDK is launching Obits: a currency that offers holders a share in current and future revenue streams. OBITS has been created as a token hosted on OpenLedger. With OBITS you can profit from all the transactions carried out on an up-and-coming cryptocurrency exchange. Buying OBITS is the equivalent of buying a stake in our exchange’s business. Not only will you share the profits but you will also have a say in the future development of OpenLedger via our exclusive voting features.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20309.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20136.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>website</label>
					<url>http://www.obits.io/</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-20T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>BitCash - Digital Money of the Future!</title>
			<description>BitCash as a product is another name for SmartCoins, a revolutionary money that people can transform into digital equivalents of US Dollars, Euro, Yuan, gold &amp; even Bitcoin. BitCash as a company is a simple bitUSD-only wallet provider for the Bitshares ecosystem that plans to have a beta product at the very beginning of the new year.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20125.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-11-03T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Plasma? The holy grail of the crypto DEX?</title>
			<description>BM hinted at a new project called plasma in a mumble session which would allow interoperability between chains. With plasma, the user can deposit btc backed by actual on-chain btc instead of btc collateralized by bts, eliminating the worry about margin maintenance and liquidity.  This would allow a much more seamless user trading experience, at least among various blockchain assets.  In other words, users would be able to trade pairs such as btc/eth while knowing that the assets are completely accounted for on the native chains.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,19728.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-10-27T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>IOTA + Bitshares</title>
			<description>IOTA is a lightweight, blockless micro-transactions token aimed specifically at Internet-of-Things (IoT). It seems that Bitshares is not aiming for micro-transactions and instead focusing on its strengths. One of IOTA's goals is to find overlap and collaborate with the serious blockchain projects as we see no reason to 'compete', instead we rather compliment the blockchain projects.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,19534.0.html</url>
				</link>
				<link>
					<label>website</label>
					<url>http://iotatoken.com/</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
		<item>
			<timestamp>2015-10-23T00:00</timestamp>
			<title>Nexus and BitShares</title>
			<description>The team behind Maker is now in the process of branding ourselves as a company with a business model similar to Cryptonomex - they call ourselves Nexus and will focus on dapp development and development as a service.</description>
			<links>
				<link>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,19418.0.html</url>
				</link>
			</links>
		</item>
	</items>
</root>
