<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- <?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="temp.xsl"?> -->
<root>
	<items>
		<item>
			<item>
				<who>puppies</who>
				<quote>Rather than just whining about the fed, or attempting to join the mafia with the hopes that we can change the mafia from within, BitShares is a direct attempt at competition.  If we can make the bankers and the politicians redundant, then we will have won.</quote>
				<source>
					<label>forum</label>
					<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20760.msg268152.html#msg268152</url>
				</source>
			</item>
			<who>delulo</who>
			<quote>
				<p>We are convinced that hierarchical structures in the form of states and the explicit and subtle form of violence associated is not the only possible (least evil) way to "run society". We are concerned about what technology can do in the hands of centralized power (surveillance). Yet at the same time technology has the potential to make possible a peaceful revolution providing a more effective and less violent way to coordinate interests and regulate society.</p>
				<p>Blockchain technology has the potential to not only disrupt the financial industry but to reduce the need for governmental regulation to protect citizens.</p>
				<p>Disrupting the financial industry needs a wider vision about what technology can do for society and in which way it can take over functions of the state because the financial industry and the wider financial and monetary system are explicitly bound to and a part of the state.</p>
				<p>It would be fatal to ignore reality if you are serious about the purpose of freedom: In order to have a lasting effect blockchain solutions have to be designed for the masses which implies high scalability, an intuitive user experience (simplicity) and an approach that pays respect to existing regulatory constraints. We are committed to profitability and maximizing capital efficiency in order to reach our goals with the necessary endurance and capital.</p>
			</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg259060.html#msg259060</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>luckybit</who>
			<quote>The concept we should promote in my opinion is to help people to become more resilient, to help people to reduce their dependency on governments and large corporations, to allow people to work directly for the blockchain, to allow people to be left alone.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258763.html#msg258763</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>bytemaster</who>
			<quote>My mission in life has been to find free market solutions to secure life, liberty, and property. Systems that are so powerful and effective that they can render governments irrelevant. This is something that I am very passionate about and the reason why I believe most of your are here and loyal to BitShares. If we lose sight of this particular vision we lose our core belief, our mission, our "why". And without a reason why we are adrift chasing profits and losing hope when they don't come quickly enough.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258666.html#msg258666</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>Samupaha</who>
			<quote>Bitshares – because revolution has to be profitable!</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,18006.msg230555.html#msg230555</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>donkeypong</who>
			<quote>If this thing succeeds, the world will be at your fingertips. It's not just the money; it's the legitimacy and a stepping stone to greater opportunities and open doors, whether these be in the realms of finance, social change, business, politics, or whatever calling each of us has to help solve problems and make a better world.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258674.html#msg258674</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>lovejoy</who>
			<quote>I'm here because BitShares can absolutely transform the way society functions, because we can render existing structures of control obsolete, because we have a chance to rewrite the rules of the game.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258698.html#msg258698</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>Xeldal</who>
			<quote>I'm still here because of the original vision though i do feel i have lost sight of it.  Bitshares can provide the tools that will create the new systems of immutable freedom of voluntary cooperation that will be crucial in bringing about a new system of control that is localized squarely with the individual.  I am whole heatedly on board for the ideas of civil disobedience and I see the state or government as the largest obstacle to a free and prosperous, peaceful society.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258703.html#msg258703</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>rgcrypto</who>
			<quote>The reason why is because this project was built upon a mission: To Secure Life, Liberty and Property. Knowing that people rallied around that idea, built a community and an amazing technology is something that keeps me around.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258725.html#msg258725</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>Akado</who>
			<quote>The reason why I'm here is - also because of the community, ideals and the fact I can vote and know my vote actually counts in building the future - is mainly because of my naive dream of ending with corruption. But maybe we can help decrease it a bit. I'd be happy if that was achieved.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258728.html#msg258728</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>CLains</who>
			<quote>Bitcoin has an essential role to play in this narrative being the seed of a native value for this alien web of interconnections. We take this achievement to heart and accelerate and generalize its impact to include complete financial independence starting with the essential exchange of value. These and associated information technologies will ensure that economic friction will approach zero as the internet matures. We are a potentially essential piece in an event of unimaginable significance. To downplay the role of both decentralization and anonymity in building an exchange is to mispercieve the exponential future of value transfers and the impossibility of traditional structures to adapt adequately. Decentralized exchange, prediction markets and equity crowd-funding and other things beside.. Imagine how Wikipedia, the Pirate Party, Anonymous, and all other internet natives are free to flourish when value flows freely. We fear our weakness now, but soon we'll fear our strength.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258731.html#msg258731</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>yvv</who>
			<quote>Most of people in the world are not bothered by governments and are not sick with any libertarian dreams. Most of people think about much simpler things like what will I eat tomorrow or how will I raise my kids. This is the reason why NASDAQ and Forex exist. People consume huge amount of stuff every day, many of which is produced over seas. NASDAQ and Forex help them to satisfy their needs, being the link between producers and consumers. They offer end solution. None of crypto projects can take their place, because all of them are made by libertarian dreamers, who don't understand how thing which they buy every day, appear in their supermarkets. Crypto is useless even for such simple things like cross border money transfer for remittance or online shopping purpose. Just a cool toy with farts and whistles, attracting curious tech geeks, who do not mind to lose money gambling against each other. I am following this blockchain tech for about three years, and hoping that at least one project will come out which is attached to real world economy.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258744.html#msg258744</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>luckybit</who>
			<quote>
				<p>Financial independence is why anyone would be here whether they love or hate government, libertarian or not. The concept we should promote in my opinion is to help people to become more resilient, to help people to reduce their dependency on governments and large corporations, to allow people to work directly for the blockchain, to allow people to be left alone.</p>
				<p>People also want to be able to survive without having to depend on government handouts, and without having to depend on an employer. Can Bitshares make all of these practical desires possible? If the answer is yes then you can build an ecosystem around financial independence alone, without the need for any other concept. I think Bitshares should simply promote financial independence.</p>
				<p>Bytemaster can have his grand ideology, his philosophy, and it's all respectable, but we should not expect a majority of people to understand any of it. Most people don't have degrees in political philosophy, and don't know or have faith in any of that. People simply want the American dream which in my opinion Bitshares and the concept of the DAC are in a position to completely re-imagine. Present a new dream, which invites everyone regardless of ideology or politics, to interact with the blockchain, to live a better and safer life.</p>
				<p>Protesters aren't always after a better or safer life. Protesters are looking to sacrifice for others, to go to prison for their beliefs when necessary, to in some cases die for their beliefs, but we shouldn't expect that all Bitshares users are going to be protesters, nor should the function of Bitshares be for protest. Bitshares should be a decentralized exchange and nothing else. Apps built around it can be for protesting, or apps UIAs can be protest UIAs, but I don't think the entire Bitshares should get caught up in that and lose focus on financial independence which is a mainstream dream.</p>
			</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258763.html#msg258763</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>BunkerChain Labs</who>
			<quote>Sustainability, security, innovation, freedom, and profit. I am here because I believe BitShares can be the bridge from government fiat to people driven currency.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258780.html#msg258780</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>roadscape</who>
			<quote>
				<p>I'm here because I believe P2P can change the world for the better.. before cryptocurrency I didn't see any feasible solutions for our growing systemic problems. Bitcoin was eye-opening but DPOS took it much further.</p>
				<p>I'm not here for the dex in particular.. I want to see usable e-2-e encryption, better identity management, secure DNS, transparent governance &amp; voting, micropayments &amp; profitable open-source, DACs, reputation systems, etc etc... but we need to start somewhere and the dex &amp; MPA's are a good foundation (or will be.. soon.. hopefully).</p>
			</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258781.html#msg258781</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>merockstar</who>
			<quote>Why am I here? After becoming acquainted with Bitcoin as a user/non-holder, I realized during one of the bubbles that there's money to be made. That is what piqued my interest and got me to learning about it, and as I did, I realized that it was much bigger than just a safer alternative to liberty reserve, or just a way to buy some weed. When the blockchain clicked I saw that the implications for the world ran much deeper. This is about the time alt-coins first started arriving on the scene, and this is how I ended up here. It would be a lie for me to say that profit wasn't the original thing that got me interested in crypto.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258786.html#msg258786</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>Helikopterben</who>
			<quote>Its seems to me that a decentralized exchange and financial freedom go hand-in-hand... so I think the vision is stronger than ever.  Legacy exchanges that are now regulated still carry substantial risks of default.  Just because a goxing hasn't occured in a while doesn't mean that is the end of it.  Its almost guaranteed to happen again.  The custodian model simply does not work and let's not forget the lessons of the 2008 financial crisis.  Goxings occured on a very large scale but were masked by bailouts and monetary inflation.  Just because losses were socialized doesn't mean that many financial institutions didn't fail.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258821.html#msg258821</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>BTSdac</who>
			<quote>I think BTS can been a tool to civil disobedience and peaceful tax protests, but the purpose is not for it. Like a gun, it can kill but also can protect. It is neutral, it is neither  good nor bad, it is just make people have equal power no matter if you are high or short, strong or weak.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258872.html#msg258872</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>Samupaha</who>
			<quote>I'm here because I believe the world needs a financial revolution. Bitshares is the most promising tool for revolution that I know. Most revolutions fail because they just overthrow the old power and don't give anything better instead. People are left in a chaotic situation and usually some evil power will rise and take control. The revolution is wasted and many times people are left in a worse situation than that what made them to start the revolution in the first place. The proper way to have a revolution is to make sure first that there exists something better that people can actually start to use when the old power is overthrown. I believe Bitshares is a great tool that can help us replace this big mess where financial markets have gone. When the next financial crisis comes, we can start to drift away from banks and other financial institutions and replace their services with Bitshares and the whole ecosystem that has been growing around it.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258948.html#msg258948</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>brainbug</who>
			<quote>Freedom, decentralized exchanges, currencies, coins, assets are nicely scalable, but the new black is elsewhere. We believe it is "securitization of things". UIA (and so on) could serve as the perfect basis for this! Agreed, other crypto coins support a couple of the required features too, but Bitshares is unique in that it offers virtually all the goodies, not just one or a few of them.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258952.html#msg258952</url>
			</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<who>jcalfee1</who>
			<quote>I'm for making long-term governance obsolete and I want to see it happen quickly and peacefully. I do this because I woke up to the emotions I feel when I hear human lives are being been lost. So I encourage you to find your friends and fight for a greater cause. I believe as most of us do, BitShares is positioned to be the best tool for the people. This is not enough though. The technology alone does not provide all of the motivation I need. It is the shocking material that I find that does the trick.</quote>
			<source>
				<label>forum</label>
				<url>https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php/topic,20123.msg258997.html#msg258997</url>
			</source>
		</item>
<!-- 		<item> -->
<!-- 			<who></who> -->
<!-- 			<quote></quote> -->
<!-- 			<source> -->
<!-- 				<label>forum</label> -->
<!-- 				<url></url> -->
<!-- 			</source> -->
<!-- 		</item> -->
	</items>
</root>