<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- <?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="temp.xsl"?> -->
<root>
	<items>
		<item>
			<feature>How new smart-contracts are deployed?</feature>
			<BitShares>Deploying a new smart-contract requires a hard-fork which is very easy to implement as all is needed is a consensus among 51% of the witness nodes.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Everybody can create and deploy a smart-contract without asking for anyone's permission.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>Deploying a new smart-contract requires passing automated tests for the code's semantics.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>What is the best analogy to the process of smart-contracts deployment?</feature>
			<BitShares>Apple Store - in this case quality of the "apps" deployed is verified by BitShares shareholders.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Google's Play - anybody can deploy anything.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>TauChain's approach is quite unprecedented as total freedom goes hand-in-hand with a guarantee regarding safety &amp; quality of the code.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>How is the original business model behind a smart-contract protected?</feature>
			<BitShares>Shareholders are able to block deployments of smart-contracts aiming to duplicate existing functionalities.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>No protection.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>No protection.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>Can businesses profit directly from fees earned by smart-contracts which turn out to be popular?</feature>
			<BitShares>Yes, by using Fee-Backed Assets.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Yes</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>Yes</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>Are businesses encouraged to build &amp; deploy general-purpose smart-contracts (i.e. not related to any particular business)?</feature>
			<BitShares>Yes, by using Worker Proposals.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>No</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>No</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>What entity receives revenues generated by smart-contracts?</feature>
			<BitShares>All shareholders by default. However by using Fee-Backed Assets it is possible to construct smart-contracts with a revenue distribution aimed at businesses that created them.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Businesses that created them.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>Businesses that created them.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>What is the programming language offered for creating smart-contracts?</feature>
			<BitShares>C++</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Several higher-level languages such as Serpent (Python inspired), Mutan (Go inspired) or LLL (LISP inspired)</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>Not known at this stage, as a new programming language paradigm will have to be invented.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>Is the smart-contract language Turing-complete?</feature>
			<BitShares>Yes</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Yes</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>No. TauChain's assumption is that Turing-completeness is not essential for most smart-contracts.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>How lethal smart-contracts are prevented &amp; eliminated?</feature>
			<BitShares>Prevented before deployment. A smart-contract's source code is trusted as it is reviewed by shareholders before being deployed.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Prevented during run-time. A smart-contract's execution is constantly monitored during run-time.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>Prevented before deployment. A smart-contract's source code is trusted as it is verified by automated tests.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>What are the consequences of the chosen lethal-code prevention method in terms of blockchain efficiency?</feature>
			<BitShares>None, smart-contracts are executed at top speed.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Huge, smart-contracts' execution is significantly slowed-down by the monitoring process.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>None, smart-contracts are executed at top speed.</TauChain>
		</item>
		<item>
			<feature>What are the consequences of the chosen lethal-code prevention method in terms of safety &amp; unmanageable hard-forks?</feature>
			<BitShares>They are unaffected.</BitShares>
			<Ethereum>Constant danger of unknown loopholes in the system.</Ethereum>
			<TauChain>They are unaffected.</TauChain>
		</item>

		
	</items>
</root>
